Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series VI is arranged in 27 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series VI. LABOR ORGANIZATIONS
  - Sub-Series 204-0. Labor Organizations
    - General, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 56)
      March 1, 1962-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - General, 1959-1962 (Box 27, Folder 57)
      1959-Feb. 28, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 204-1. Labor Organizations
    - Airline Pilots Association, 1957-1961 (Box 27, Folder 58)
      June 1, 1957-June 30, 1961.
    - Airline Pilots Association, 1932-1957 (Box 27, Folder 59)
      1932-May 31, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 204-2. Labor Organizations
    - Automobile, Aircraft, etc. Workers, 1958-1962 (Box 27, Folder 60)
      1958-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 204-15. Labor Organizations
    - Conductors and Brakemen, Order of, 1933-1962 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      1933-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 204-16. Labor Organizations
    - American Train Dispatchers Association, 1924-1943 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      1924-Dec. 1943.
  - Sub-Series 204-18. Labor Organizations
    - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1933-1954 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 204-20. Labor Organizations
    - Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1922-1953 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 204-22. Labor Organizations
    - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1922-1966 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      1922-Jan. 15, 1966.
  - Sub-Series 204-23. Labor Organizations
    - International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1922-1937 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 204-24. Labor Organizations
    - Flight Engineers International Association, 1959-1961 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Jan. 1, 1959-Dec. 31, 1961.
    - Flight Engineers International Association, 1948-1958 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      Jan. 1, 1948-Dec. 31, 1958.
  - Sub-Series 204-25. Labor Organizations
    - Garment Workers Union, International Ladies, 1957-1963 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Jan. 1, 1957-Dec. 31, 1963.
  - Sub-Series 204-31. Labor Organizations
    - Longshoremens' Association International, 1925-1962 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Jan. 1, 1925-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 204-32. Labor Organizations
    - International Association of Machinists, 1924-1962 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      1924-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 204-41. Labor Organizations
    - Porters, Brotherhood of Sleeping Car, 1927-1959 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Jan. 1, 1927-Dec. 31, 1959.
  - Sub-Series 204-43. Labor Organizations
    - Railway Employees' Department, 1957-1964 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      Jan. 1, 1957-Dec. 31, 1964.
  - Sub-Series 204-46. Labor Organizations
    - Seafarers International Union, 1960-1963 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Jan. 1, 1960-Dec. 31, 1963.
  - Sub-Series 204-48. Labor Organizations
    - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, 1956-1964 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Jan. 1, 1956-Dec. 31, 1964.
    - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, 1922-1955 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      1922-Dec. 1955.
  - Sub-Series 204-50. Labor Organizations
    - Steelworkers of America, United, 1956-1962 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      1956-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 204-52. Labor Organizations
    - Supervisors Association, American Railway, 1951-1963 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      Jan. 1, 1951-Dec. 31, 1963.
  - Sub-Series 204-53. Labor Organizations
    - Switchmens' Union of North America, 1924-1960 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      1924-Dec. 31, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 204-55. Labor Organizations
    - Teamsters, International Brotherhood of, 1958-1961 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      Jan. 1, 1958-Dec. 31, 1961.
  - Sub-Series 204-57. Labor Organizations
    - Report of G.E. Leighty, President, The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      June, 1964.
    - Telegraphers, Order of Railroad, 1963-1964 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      Nov. 1, 1963-May 31, 1964.
    - Transportation Communication Employees Union, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      Jan. 1, 1963-Oct. 31, 1963.
    - Report of G.E. Leighty, President, The Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      June, 1956.
    - Telegraphers, Order of Railroad, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      Nov. 12, 1962-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - Telegraphers, Order of Railroad, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      Jan. 1, 1961-Aug. 31, 1962.
    - Telegraphers, Order of Railroad, 1956-1960 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      Jan. 1, 1956-Dec. 31, 1960.
    - Report of G.E. Leighty, President, The Order of Railroad Telegraphers (bound volume), 1960 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      June, 1960.
    - Policy Declarations. Third Division. National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Order of Railroad Telegraphers Strike, Atlantic Coast Line, 1925-1926 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Order of Railroad Telegraphers Strike, Georgia and Florida Railroads, 1924-1925 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Order of Railroad Telegraphers Strike Ballot, Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railroad, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Order of Railroad Telegraphers National Bank, 1933-1934 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Order of Railroad Telegraphers Bank, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Order of Railroad Telegraphers, General, 1932-1955 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      1932-Dec. 1955.
  - Sub-Series 204-63. Labor Organizations
    - Trainmen, Brotherhood of Railroad, 1959-1962 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      Jan. 1, 1959-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - Trainmen, Brotherhood of Railroad, 1947-1958 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      Jan. 1, 1947-Dec. 31, 1958.
    - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. General, 1932-1946 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1925-1931 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 204-65. Labor Organizations
    - Typographical Union, International, 1950-1960 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      Jan. 1, 1950-Dec. 31, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 204-68. Labor Organizations
    - Yardmasters of America, Railroad, 1931-1962 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      Jan. 1, 1931-Dec. 31, 1962.
  - Sub-Series 294-69. Labor Organizations
    - Maintenance of Way Employees, Brotherhood, 1963-1964 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      Jan. 1, 1963-Dec. 31, 1964.
    - Report of H.C. Crotty, President, Thirty-Fourth Regular Convention-Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      July 9, 1962. Bound volume.
    - Maintenance of Way Employees, Brotherhood, 1961-1962 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      June 1, 1961-Dec. 31, 1962.
    - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees. Proceedings of the Thirty-fourth Regular Grand Lodge Convention. (bound volume), 1962 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      July 9-13, 1962.
    - Maintenance of Way Employees, Brotherhood, 1957-1961 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Jan. 1, 1957-May 31, 1961.
    - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1933-1956 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      1933-Dec. 1956.
    - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1922-1932 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 204-73. Labor Organizations
    - National Maritime Union of America, 1960-1962. (Box 33, Folder 5)
      1960-Dec. 31, 1962.